>> Brian Holt: 所以说，嘿，我需要一个钥匙，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So it's saying,
hey, I need a key, so
让我们再谈这事
let's talk about that for just a second.
那么，在重新呈现这一过程中， " 反应 " 如何呢 ?
So how does React work in
terms of like rerendering it?
每当发生更改时，它会在此处运行 reender 函数，对吗 ?
Everytime that something changes,
it runs the rerender function here, right?
因此，它再次运行此 searchParams 函数。
So it runs this searchParams
function again.
我想让你想象这些选择可能更加复杂。
I want you to imagine that maybe
these options were more complicated.
也许他们对 DOM 结构的内缩有很深的影响
Maybe they were deeply of
necetries of DOM structures, so
让我们说我有能力用这种方式来选择
let's say I had the ability to resort
these options one way or another.
雷act通常会看到的是
Well, what React would typically see is,
这跟以前不一样了我要把所有东西都重新呈现
this is different than it was before,
I'm gonna go rerender everything.
但如果我只是用不同的顺序
But if I'm just resorting
them into a different order,
这将是一个非常必要的工作，相当缓慢，很可能。
that would be a lot of a necessary work,
quite slow, potentially.
什么是有用的，比如，嘿， React，我刚刚重新订了这些。
What would be really useful, is like,
hey, React, I just reordered these.
我没有创造和
I didn't actually create and
毁了一切他们现在的顺序就不同了
destroy anything,
they're just in a different order now.
你能做到这一点你可以说
And the way you can do
that is you can say,
key = 关于该特定项的一些唯一的东西。
key = some unique thing
about that particular item.
在这种情况下，它们都是字符串，我知道它们都不同。
In this case they're all strings and
I know they're all different.
所以如果我说键 = [动物] 那就开心了，
So if I say key =
[animal] then it's happy,
因为它说如果狗在这里但现在它在下面
because then it says if dog was here,
but now it's down here.
就像我要选择那样我才不会毁了它
It's like I'm just going to take that
option, I'm not gonna destroy it,
我要把它移到下面这才是关键
I'm just gonna move it down there,
so that's what key does.
所以这是一个非常容易做到的表演。
So it's a little performance
thing that's really easy to do.
所以这里的关键是，它应该是一个独特的标识符，
So the key here is, it needs to be some
sort of unique identifier about that
特定对象，对吗 ?
particular object, right?
因此，如果您正在对用户对象进行排序，那么可以通过电子邮件对其进行排序，或者
So maybe if you're sorting user objects,
you can sort it by the email, or
他们的用户身份或者每个用户都是唯一的
their user ID, or
something that's gonna be unique per user.
然后，如果它在这里移动，然后在这里移动，它是一样的。
Then if it moves here, and then it
moves down here, it is the same thing.
所以， React 可以告诉它是一回事，有道理吗 ?
So that React can tell it's
the same thing, makes sense?
现在重要的是它必须是唯一的，所以如果我放了 1 个，对吧 ?
Now something that's really important is
it has to be unique, so if I put 1, right?
现在所有这些都要有 1 个钥匙而且要疯了
Now all of these are gonna have a key
of 1 and is going to freak out.
>> Brian Holt: 它会说，嘿，我遇到的是同一个键 1。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's gonna say, hey,
I encountered with the same key 1.
这对我来说没道理所以如果你这样做会很奇怪的
That doesn't make any sense to me, so
it'll do weird things if you do that.
>> Brian Holt: 在这种情况下，它实际上是在渲染它们，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: In this case, it actually
is rendering them, so good for that,
但有时它不会让它们发生
but sometimes it just won't render them.
所以，确保它实际上是独一无二的。
So make sure it is actually
unique about them.